<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>ME/LC Community News</title>
    <link>https://me-cfs.github.io/news/rss/community.xml</link>
    <description/>
    <item>
      <title>Black and Unbelieved: A conversation with filmmaker Chimére Sweeney</title>
      <link>https://thesicktimes.org/2024/06/04/black-and-unbelieved-a-conversation-with-filmmaker-chimere-sweeney/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=black-and-unbelieved-a-conversation-with-filmmaker-chimere-sweeney</link>
      <guid>https://thesicktimes.org/?p=2628</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming down with Covid-19 on March 22, 2020 completely altered filmmaker Chimére Sweeney’s life. A Black middle school English teacher in Baltimore, Maryland at the time, Sweeney was shocked to...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org/2024/06/04/black-and-unbelieved-a-conversation-with-filmmaker-chimere-sweeney/"&gt;Black and Unbelieved: A conversation with filmmaker Chimére Sweeney&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org"&gt;The Sick Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <source>The Sick Times</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘They bungled it:’ NIH documents reveal how $1.6 billion Long Covid initiative has failed so far to meet its goals</title>
      <link>https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/31/they-bungled-it-nih-documents-reveal-how-1-6-billion-long-covid-initiative-has-failed-so-far-to-meet-its-goals/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=they-bungled-it-nih-documents-reveal-how-1-6-billion-long-covid-initiative-has-failed-so-far-to-meet-its-goals</link>
      <guid>https://thesicktimes.org/?p=2603</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In February 2021, the National Institutes of Health launched a new $1 billion initiative to study Long Covid, a chronic disease that has changed the lives of millions of Americans. Three years later, the NIH initiative, called RECOVER, has not met these goals, according to a detailed review of budget and planning documents obtained through the Freedom of Information Act and shared with Long Covid experts. RECOVER’s research into Long Covid’s underlying biology has lagged behind that of privately-funded scientists; it has failed to provide reliable estimates of how many people have Long Covid; and clinical trials, launched last summer, garnered extensive criticism for failing to test promising treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/31/they-bungled-it-nih-documents-reveal-how-1-6-billion-long-covid-initiative-has-failed-so-far-to-meet-its-goals/"&gt;‘They bungled it:’ NIH documents reveal how $1.6 billion Long Covid initiative has failed so far to meet its goals&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org"&gt;The Sick Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <source>The Sick Times</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Covid advocates call out Biden, ask for $1.2 billion of 2025 NIH budget</title>
      <link>https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/28/long-covid-advocates-demand-portion-of-2025-nih-budget/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=long-covid-advocates-demand-portion-of-2025-nih-budget</link>
      <guid>https://thesicktimes.org/?p=2579</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week, a delegation organized by the grassroots advocacy group the Long Covid Campaign traveled to Washington D.C., asking Senate leaders to accelerate over a billion dollars in funding for...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/28/long-covid-advocates-demand-portion-of-2025-nih-budget/"&gt;Long Covid advocates call out Biden, ask for $1.2 billion of 2025 NIH budget&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org"&gt;The Sick Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <source>The Sick Times</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make spaces more accessible during the continuing pandemic</title>
      <link>https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/23/how-to-make-spaces-more-accessible-during-the-continuing-pandemic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-make-spaces-more-accessible-during-the-continuing-pandemic</link>
      <guid>https://thesicktimes.org/?p=2546</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The relentlessness of the pandemic, now in its fifth year, is drawn out by the persistence of its denial. The federal emergency ended, Covid-19 precautions have been lifted for years, and though many people are “back to normal,” over 20,000 people in the United States died of Covid-19 since the beginning of 2024. Millions who avoided death are nonetheless still living with Long Covid, and this number grows each month. We are still in crisis. This is alarming, but it’s no reason to abandon hope or freeze in inaction. A blueprint for radical inclusion and living a full, safer life within the context of Covid-19 exists. Many mutual aid groups and initiatives advocating for clean air and continued Covid-19 safety are emerging all over the world using technology and layers of protection to help mitigate the spread of viruses. As an access worker at All Kinds and a founder of Clean Air Club, we are part of this multifaceted effort: we believe that focusing on layered mitigation strategies is one way to protect the health and safety of our communities and create accessible futures in the here and now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/23/how-to-make-spaces-more-accessible-during-the-continuing-pandemic/"&gt;How to make spaces more accessible during the continuing pandemic&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org"&gt;The Sick Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <source>The Sick Times</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten new books about Long Covid, chronic illness, and disability</title>
      <link>https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/21/ten-new-books-about-long-covid-chronic-illness-and-disability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ten-new-books-about-long-covid-chronic-illness-and-disability</link>
      <guid>https://thesicktimes.org/?p=2501</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2022 brought us some of the first books on Long Covid, including The Long Covid Survival Guide, The Long Haul, and The Long Covid Handbook. Now, as we forge into the fifth year of the Covid-19 pandemic, more books and anthologies are emerging authored by people with Long Covid and related conditions, as well as broader disability narratives reflecting on the pandemic. Here are ten recently published books on Long Covid, Myalgic Encephalomyelitis (ME), chronic illness, and disability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org/2024/05/21/ten-new-books-about-long-covid-chronic-illness-and-disability/"&gt;Ten new books about Long Covid, chronic illness, and disability&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://thesicktimes.org"&gt;The Sick Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <source>The Sick Times</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>